WYATT REVALEE

Terre Haute, Indiana · (618) 553-0037
wyatt.revalee@gmail.com / wrevalee@sycamores.indstate.edu
website: wyatt-revalee.netlify.app

SKILLS / CODING EXPERIENCE

APRIL 2023

REACT DEVELOPMENT REACT / MONGODB

With graduation around the corner, I wanted to round out my portfolio with a more "real-world" type of project, and I settled on building a social media app using React, with REST API and MongoDB. While react seemed to me like an advanced form of html, the experience was invaluable as it taught me so much about connecting the front-end and back-end, as well as sending and receiving web requests.

JUNE 2022 - PRESENT

VIDEOGAME DEVELOPMENT UNITY ENGINE – C#

In the summer of 2022, I started developing my own game with Unity Engine. It applies a lot of my knowledge I've obtained from school over my four years, as well as pushed me to learn another language (C#). Code and demo are available on my website and GitHub.

AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT

SCHOOL CODING WORK INDIANA STATE UNIVERSITY

There have been a lot of assignments that I have worked on over the years, ranging from simple to rather complex. Some of this code I have uploaded to GitHub to be seen.

EDUCATION

MAY 2018

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, HUTSONVILLE HIGHSCHOOL

3.5 GPA, Officer of National Honor Society.

CURRENT – GRADUATION IN MAY 2023

BACHELOR'S DEGREE OF COMPUTER SCIENCE, INDIANA STATE UNIVERSITY

Currently a 2nd semester senior, graduating in the spring. 2.8 GPA.

SKILLS

- Python, JavaScript, C, C#, React, MongoDB
- Lots of teamworking experience

- Communication
- Problem Solving

WORK EXPERIENCE

JULY 2022 – DECEMBER 2022

PRINT & MARKETING TECH, STAPLES TERRE HAUTE

Many responsibilities, such as greeting customers and addressing their needs, creating and working on job tickets, maintaining the print and marketing area of the store (working with machines, ordering supplies, addressing issues, etc.), and working as a team.

JULY 2020 – JANUARY 2022

TAKEAWAY SERVER, OUTBACK STEAKHOUSE

Responsible for taking and completing orders for takeout, as well as managing the takeout team.

SEPTEMBER 2018 – FEBRUARY 2020

COMPUTER TECHNICIAN, INDIANA STATE UNIVERSITY, TECH SUPPORT CENTER

Working with software and hardware teams to create tickets, solve software issues for customers, and setting up new devices for students and faculty. As well as working front desk to address customer issues up front and assign them to a proper team to be worked on.